farbeyondthestars.com 2013-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Reading time: 2 – 3 minutes

**PRIVACY POLICY**

At HowToVanish.com the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.howtovanish.com and how it is used.

**Log Files:**

Like many other web sites, www.howtovanish.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

HowToVanish.com uses cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie:**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.howtovanish.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.howtovanish.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http//www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Valueclick, Infolinks, Kontera and others:

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.howtovanish.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

HowToVanish.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers:

You should check the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.howtovanish.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

5,103 random numbers[](http://www.howtovanish.com/legal-disclaimer/privacy-policy/emailpage/ "Email") [Email](http://www.howtovanish.com/legal-disclaimer/privacy-policy/emailpage/ "Email") [](http://www.howtovanish.com/legal-disclaimer/privacy-policy/printpage/ "Print") [Print](http://www.howtovanish.com/legal-disclaimer/privacy-policy/printpage/ "Print")

### [Be first to comment](http://www.howtovanish.com/legal-disclaimer/privacy-policy/#comments)

**ABOUT THE AUTHOR:** Trace Mayer, J.D., holds a degree in Accounting, a law degree from [California Western School of Law](http://www.cwsl.edu/ "California Western School of Law") and studies the Austrian school of economics. He works as an entrepreneur, investor, journalist, monetary scientist and operates [Run To Gold](http://www.runtogold.com/ "Run To Gold"). He is a strong advocate of the freedom of speech, a member of the Society of Professional Journalists and the San Diego County Bar Association. He has appeared on ABC, NBC, BNN, many radio shows and presented at many investment conferences throughout the world. This is merely one article of 41 by . 

---|---
